Guide to the Gligor Tashkovich papers,1983-2015.
Tashkovich, Gligor papers,1983-2015.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gligor Tashkovich papers, 1983-2015.
41-5-3039
Gligor. Tashkovich
31.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, memorabilia, photographs, printed materials, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files relating to student and alumni activities and campus governance including the Committee to Review the Dean of Students Office, Quill and Dagger, the Public Safety Advisory Board, the Campus Store Administrative Board, and the Budget Policies Committee, the Career Center of the Johnson Graduate School of Management, and fundraising efforts for the Johnson School and for the Campus Life Campaign Committee (with memorabilia from the campaign). Also, "Helping Cornell Begin its Journey Towards Legendary Service: Highways, Bumpy Roads and Potholes," by Kenneth Blanchard and Gligor Tashkovich. Program for 1984 memorial service for Erin Nieswand and Young Hee Suh, students murdered in 1983, 1984, with photographs of memorial trees and plaque dedicated to their memory. Folder with material concerning the Membership Solicitation Program. Clippings relating to the Cornell Board of Trustees and the Student Assembly.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University Class of 1987, M.B.A. '91. In 2006, he was named Minister for Foreign Investment in the new Government in the Republic of Macedonia.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files relating to student and alumni activities and campus governance.
Also, holiday cards and other correspondence relating to Cornell activities, and letters from Cornell units about 9/11.
Files of brochures, programs, invitations, etc. relating to Seal & Serpent, the College of Arts & Sciences, the Johnson School of Management, the Law School, and the College of Veterinary Medicine; to the Cornell Association of Class Officers, the Asian Alumni Association, the Chimes, the Big Red Band, the Johnson Art Museum, the Library, and the Plantations. Also, program from the NAACP National Equal Justice Award Dinner honoring Jeffrey Lehman.
Also, materials relating to Macedonia, Albania, Azerbaijan, Bulgaria, Rumania, and other Balkan countries. Including files about the Center for Civil and Human Rights (CCHR), the only organization dedicated to serving the needs of and advocating for the LGBT community in Macedonia. Files relating to the Council on Foreign Relations. Copies of "Russian Petroleum Investor," 1994-1999; and other materials on oil pipelines. Materials relating to the elections in Kazakhstan for which Tashkovich was an election observer, 2004. T-shirts from the Olympics in Sidney, Australia, 2000; Athens, 2004; and Beijing, 2008; hat from Salt Lake City Olympics, 2002.
Also, items collected after becoming Minister for Foreign Investment, Republic of Macedonia.
Holiday cards and invitations from Macedonia, 2006.
File of about 90 (Nigerian) advance-fee scam Internet letters, collected by Tashkovich.
T-shirt for Bidzina Ivanishvili from the October 1, 2012 Parliamentary elections in Georgia, the election in which billionaire Ivanishvili's opposition Georgian Dream coalition won a majority of seats
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tashkovich, Gligor.; Blanchard, Kenneth H.; Lehman, Jeffrey S.; McMillan, L. Londell.; Nieswand, Erin.; Suh, Young Hee.; Cornell Association of Class Officers.; Cornell Campus Store.Administrative Board.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University.Class of 1987.; Cornell University.Office of the Dean of Students.; Cornell University.Board of Trustees.; Cornell University.Student Assembly.; Cornell University.College of Arts and Sciences.; Cornell University.School of Hotel Administration.; Cornell University.Big Red Marching Band.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)--Alumni and alumnae.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University); New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.; Quill and Dagger Society (Cornell University); Seal & Serpent Society (Cornell University).; Olympic Games; Olympic Games; Olympic Games; Winter Olympic Games
Subjects:
Fund raising.; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.; Homosexuality--Macedonia.; Elections--Kazakhstan.
Places:
Macedonia--Social conditions.; Macedonia--Economic conditions.; Macedonia--Politics and government.; Bulgaria--Social conditions.; Kazakhstan--Politics and government.; Albania--Social life and customs.; Romania
Form and Genre Terms:
CD-ROMS.; DVDs.; Floppy disks.; Scrapbooks.; T-shirts.; Greeting cards.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Series List
Series I. FAMILY/PERSONAL.
Box 1, 28, 34-37, 39
Series II. CORRESPONDENCE.
Boxes 1, 18
Series III. CORNELL UNIVERSITY: Under-graduate Materials.
Boxes 18-26
Series IV. CORNELL UNIVERSITY: Post-graduate Materials.
Boxes 1-8, 23-24, 28, 33, 38
Series V. UNITED STATES.
Boxes 7-9, 23, 30, 33, 38
Series VI. INTERNATIONAL COMMITTEES.
Boxes 10-11
Series VII. INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS.
Boxes 11-15, 27-30, 32, 33, 38
Series VIII. MISCELLANY
Boxes 2, 6, 16-17, 23-24, 31, 32, 38
Series IX. AUDIO/VISUAL MATERIAL
CONTAINER LIST
- SERIES I. FAMILY/PERSONAL
  - Family history, 2001, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Passports, 1988-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Personal, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cards, 1970's-1980's (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Cards, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Cards, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Cards, 1992-2002 (Box 34)
  - Cards, 2002-2006 (Box 35)
  - Cards, 2006-2012 (Box 36)
  - Cards, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 1-8)
  - Cards, 2013-2014 (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
  - Cards, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 7-10)
  - Boarding Passes, 2007 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2003 - 2008 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1999 - 2005 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Papers from conferences and a member handbook.
  - Holiday Cards, 2007 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Stays, 2006 - 2008 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Invitations - Folder 1, 2006 - 2014 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Invitations - Folder 2, 2007 - 2010 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Invitations - Folder 3, 2006 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Menus - Folder 1, 2006 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Some menus are undated
  - Menus - Folder 2, 2015 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2012 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Playboy Bunny sticker
  - Nutrition Pamphlets, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Performance Programs, 2006 - 2010 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence - Folder 1, 1983 - 1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence - Folder 2, 2009 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Playbills - Folder 1, 2011 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Playbills - Folder 2, 2011 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    Includes autograph from George Takei.
  - Programs, 2009 - 2015 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Included Cornell material. Gligor noted that Vinton Chef, a "Father of the Internet," is his cousin through his mother's side of his family.
  - Tickets, 2015 - 2016 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate College Application Process, 1982 - 1983 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Name tags and IDs (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Wrigley Christmas card, Cornell reunion buttons, and pens (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Pen used in Parliament (Box 47)
  - Foreign language books on Macedonia and Turkmenistan (Box 47)
  - Books on Macedonian culture (Box 47)
  - HEC apron (Box 47)
  - Macedonian Police Shirt (Box 47)
  - Alexander the Great: King of Macedonia shirt (Box 47)
  - OSCE ODIHR arm bands (Box 47)
  - Amersafe storage bag (Box 47)
  - Menus, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Many are undated
  - Nametags and ID cards and pins (Box 48, Folder 9)
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Correspondence, 1981-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4-21)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - E-mails, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- SERIES III. CORNELL UNIVERSITY: Under-graduate Materials.
  - Course notes and notebooks (Box 18-20)
  - Student activities (Box 21-22)
  - Clippings (Box 25-26)
- SERIES IV. CORNELL UNIVERSITY: Post-graduate Materials.
  - Alumni Affairs material, 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Council, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Federation, 2001, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Federation - Rhodes dinner, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Mentoring, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - American Indian Program, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Fund, 2008-2012 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    -SAS, Lab of Ornithology, Fraternity and Sorority Advisory Council
  - Architecture, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Architecture reorganization, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arecibo, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Arts & Sciences, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
  - Asian-American Studies Program, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Asian Alumni Association, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Athletics, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 35-36)
  - Big Red Band, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 37-38)
  - Big Red Band Notes, 2009-2012 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Biology, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Kenneth Blanchard - Students as Customers, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Budget Policies Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - CACO material, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - CACO Board Notebook (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Alumni Admissions Ambassador Network (CAAAN), 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 42-46)
  - CAAAN, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Cornell Association of Class Officers (CACO), 1990-2006 (Box 3, Folder 3-9)
  - [Cornell] Campus governance and trustees, 1983-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - [Cornell] Campus governance: clippings, 1988-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Campaign Committee: Campus Life, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Campus Store Administrative Board, 1986-1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Adult University (CAU) trip to Antarctica, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Cayuga Society, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Black Alumni Association (CBAA), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Career Services, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - [Cornell] Chimes, 1991-2007 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - [Cornell] Chimes, 2008-2013 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Information Technologies (CIT), 1989-2006 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - [Cornell] Class Activities, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - [Cornell] Class of 1987, 1999, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - [Cornell] Clippings, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - [Cornell] Clippings, 1995-2005 (Box 4, Folder 1-8)
  - Cornell Club of Switzerland, Directory of Members, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - [Cornell] Commencement, 2002, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Commitment, Office of, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Committee to Review Dean of Students Office, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - [Cornell] Communication and Marketing Services (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Council Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Conduct Regulation - Timeline of Important Incidents and Legislation, by Bern Weintraub, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Fund, 1999-2007 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Cornell Fund - Cornell Campaign, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Fund - Cornell Campaign: tote bag, kit, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Cornell Young Alumni Program, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - C. U. history and student government, 1982-1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - C. U. in Washington program, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Cornell - leaflets, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Cornell obituaries, 1985-2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Sun: 40th Anniversary of Straight Takeover, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Tradition, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dalai Lama visit to C. U., 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Economics, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Elections (see also "clippings"), 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Engineering, 1987-2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Ezra Magazine, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Financial Planners, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fund raising, 1987-2004 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Greek (fraternity/sorority) Life, 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 31-34)
  - Greek (fraternity/sorority) Life, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hillel, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Hip songs, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Homecoming, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hotel School, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Housing, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Human Ecology, 2004-2007 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Humanities, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Inaugural Committee, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Public Affairs, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Institite for the Social Sciences, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - International Students, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, Menus, etc., 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Invitations & Programs, 1996-2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Johnson Art Museum, 2002-2007 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management (JGSM), 1999-2007 (Box 5, Folder 18-24)
  - Johnson School and Museum, 2007-2013 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - JGSM Career Center, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - JGSM, entrepreneurship, 1987-2004 (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
  - JGSM, fund raising, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Latino Studies Program, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Law School, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Lehman, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Lehman - NAACP, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Library, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 33-35)
  - Life Sciences, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Memorial services, 1984, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous mementos: buttons, hat, wedding souvenir, duffel bag, tote bags, frisbee, mug, professional cards, pens and pencils, a "Bend-a-bottle" from CAAA reunion (2013), an organizer, a wine glass/bottle (Box 24)
  - Miscellany, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Mosaic, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Museum catalogs, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Music, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nano Technology Facility, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Plantations, 2002-2007 (Box 6, Folder 6-9)
  - Plantations, 2005-2010 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - President Skorton Inauguration, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - President's Council of Cornell Women (PCCW), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Public Safety Advisory Board, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Quill and Dagger, 1992, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hunter Rawlings, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hunter Rawlings and Cornell, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Residence Life, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Residential Initiative, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Reunion, 1995, 2000-2007 (Box 6, Folder 18-22)
  - Reunion Run medals, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23-24)
  - Review of Non-mandatory Student Fees, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Frank Rhodes, 1987-1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Seal & Serpent, 1984-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26-38)
  - Seal & Serpent, 1997-2007 (Box 7, Folder 1-11)
  - Seal & Serpent: clippings, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Seal & Serpent Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
  - Seal & Serpent: house plans, n.d. (Box 7)
  - Spirit! Magazine, 2009-2011 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Student Trustee/Assembly, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sun Parody, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Tang Family and photo CD-ROM, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Technology Transfer Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
  - Tee shirts (Box 23)
  - Tower Club, 1989-2000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Trustee Profiles and news articles [scrapbook], 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
  - Trustees, 1989-2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Trustee/Council Materials, 1998-2004 (Box 8, Folder 1-9)
  - Trustee Council Weekend, 2002, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Trustees/Elections (see also "clippings"), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Veterinary Medicine, College of, 2000-2007 (Box 8, Folder 14-19)
  - Vice Provost for Research, 1998-2004 (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
  - Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Volunteer Recognition, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cornell miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Videocassette - Johnson School of Graduate Management, "Follies 1991", V-6745 (Box 24)
  - Videocassette - Cornell Salutes The Rhodes, 1995; V-6746 (Box 24)
  - Videocassette - Cornell: The movie, the 1986-87 video yearbook, 1986-1987; V-7028 (Box 24)
  - Videocassette - Cornell '59, the class on the cutting edge, 1959; V-7029 (Box 24)
  - Quill and Dagger, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Hotel Ezra Cornell weekend, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - CU Alumni, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Cornell material, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Sesquicentennial, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Chimes newsletter, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Misc. items regarding donations, 2015 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Trustee -Council Annual Meeting, 2015, 2017 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Big Red Band Notes, 2003 - 2010 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1987, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Newsletters, 1999 - 2005 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - College of Engineering, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Communique Magazine, 2002 - 2007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Comparative Cancer Program at Cornell, 2000 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Connecting with Cornell magazine, 2002 - 2006 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Administrative and Faculty Documents, 2002 - 2006 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Contains financial planning information, an Affirmative Action journal, an explanation for the resignation of Dean Philip Lewis, and an Admissions and Enrollment review
  - Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    A story containing Tashkovich's grandfather's letter on the first atomic bomb explosion
  - Cornell Alumni Materials - Folder 1, 2002 - 2016 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    Cornell Alumni Magazine, Seal and Serpent materials, SAS, Black Alumni Association
  - Cornell Alumni Materials - Folder 2, 2002 - 2016 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Annual Fund - Folder 1, 2006 - 2015 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Contains a metal pin
  - Cornell Annual Fund - Folder 2, 1992 - 1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Cornell - Asian/Asian American Materials, 2003 - 2016 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    Contains an AASP newsletter, a letter from the CAAA, and a publication by John F. Dean about information services in times of war in Southeast Asia.
  - Cornell Association of Class Officers - Folder 1, 2001 - 2010 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Association of Class Officers - Folder 2, 2001 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Cornell City and Regional Planning, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Donations, 2008 - 2015 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Enterprise Magazine - Folder 1, 2002 - 2004 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Enterprise Magazine - Folder 2, 2005 - 2006 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Enterprise Magazine - Folder 3, 2007 - 2008 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Hotel School - Folder 1, 2005 - 2007 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    Cornell Hotel School magazine
  - Cornell Hotel School - Folder 2, 2008 - 2009 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    Cornell Hotel School magazine and pamphlet
  - Cornell Magazines, Bulletins, and Newsletters - Folder 1, 2004 - 2016 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    Cornell Engineering, Weil Cornell Medicine, College of Agriculture and Life Sciences News, Cornell Chronicle, Cornell Political Forum, Latino Studies Program, Entrepreneurship and Personal Enterprise Program, News Notes from the Cornell Chimesmasters
  - Cornell Magazines, Bulletins, and Newsletters - Folder 2, 2004 - 2016 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Pamphlets, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Plantations, 2005 - 2010 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Cornell's Adult University, 2008 - 2010 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Cornell School of Hotel Administration, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University Council, 1997-1999 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    Includes the Preservation Survey and Conservation Training Visit to Thailand, Vietnam, and Cambodia (1991)
  - Cornell University Library, 1991 - 2010 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Veterinary Medicine, 2000 - 2009 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - eCornell, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Ezra Magazine, 2008 - 2009 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Financial Planner, 2001 - 2015 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Materials, 2000 - 2008 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Graduate School Application, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art - Folder 1, 1997 - 2016 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art - Folder 2, 2005 - 2015 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Inauguration of David J. Skorton, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - The Johnson School - Folder 1, 2001 - 2010 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - The Johnson School - Folder 2, 2003 - 2007 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - The Johnson School - Folder 3, 2002 - 2016 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Law School, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Plan to increase undergraduate scholarship endowment
  - Preserving Ezra's Vision for the 21st Century, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 2000 - 2008 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    The Snake
  - Seal and Serpent Society - Folder 1, 1987 - 2000 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Seal and Serpent Society - Folder 2, 2014 - 2015 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Newspapers, 2003 - 2007 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Spirit Magazine, 2002 - 2010 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Reunion mailings, Johnson School mailings, TCAM weekend packet, pamphlets, 2017 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- SERIES V. UNITED STATES.
  - BP - U. S. Energy, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Center for American Progress, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Citizen Democracy Corps, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Department of State: Land Mines, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - (U. S.) Dept. of the Navy, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hank Dullea political campaign items, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Rob Fersh profile, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - IH/M & RS International Hotel/Motel & Restaurant Show, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Mal Kalos [NSF & supercomputer], 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - L. Londell McMillan, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Memorials, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - NSF Network News, 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 9/11/01, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Other, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - William & Adele Rogers, 1998, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sheffield Land Trust, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 2002 Election (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - U. S. AID, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - U. S. Politics, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - War on Terror, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NYC 2009 Election related documents (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - NYC Politics, 2009-2012 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - NYC Social life: ticket stubs, 2011-2012 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - NYC Social life: invitations, announcements, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NYC Social Life: programs, play bills, 2010-2012 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - NYC Social Life: misc, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - NYC Politics, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - NYC Social Life: programs, play bills, 2013-2015 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - NYC Politics, 2014-2015 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Events, 2014-2015 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Playbills, 2014-2015 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    HIV/AIDS prevention
  - Campaign 2004: U.S. Foreign Policy in the Presidential Election, April 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Central Park Conservancy, 2014 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    Annual report
  - Columbia University, 2015 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Policy, 2006 - 2017 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    Southern Afghanistan COIN Operations, United Nations, New York Global Leaders Dialogue, National Committee on American Foreign Policy, International Crisis Group
  - National Institute of Health, June 2003 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Medicine By Design
  - New York Times, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - NSFNET, November 2007 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    National Science Foundation - celebrating the launch of the internet
  - NYC Poll Worker Manual, 2015 - 2016 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Small Enterprise Assistance Funds, July 2004 (Box 42, Folder 22)